The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Early stage Soul Formation ?
This is a great opportunity,
we should act now !
Master,
don't scare me like that.
My Origin Soul got damaged.
I need to recover as soon as possible.
Fellow cultivator,
what happened to cause you
to end up in such a state ?
Giant Demon Clan ?
A Celestial Realm fragment collapse.
Fellow cultivator,
not just anyone can escape
the collapse of a Celestial Realm fragment.
I'm Chi Hu of the Giant Demon Clan.
What's your name ?
I'm Ceng Niu.
Ceng Niu...
Is this cultivator part of
the Ceng family of the rank 5
country of Heaven Soul from Suzaku ?
He is Early stage Soul Formation at such a young age
and he can even control wandering souls...
He must be the core disciple of a rank 5 country.
Fellow cultivator,
can I come closer to talk ?
Brother Ceng,
I'll be frank with you.
Since we are both from Suzaku,
I hope you can help me.
Once you see this, you will understand.
Jade coffin
Central fragment
Rain Celestial Realm
A coffin made of celestial jades ?!
So there are such treasures in the Celestial Realm...
Brother Ceng,
that place was found many years ago
by a genius of my clan
when he came in here.
That place
is guarded by celestial beasts
and powerful restrictions.
As he wasn't powerful enough,
he didn't act recklessly.
He recorded his sight in this jade
and returned safely.
It has been many years.
It probably has been found by someone.
Not possible !
I promise you this place has not been found.
There is a reason,
but I cannot tell you right now.
Forgive me Brother Ceng.
Chi Hu and I are complete strangers
but he wants to team up with me...
He must have really liked my wandering souls.
I'm afraid it will be hard
for just the both of us to get there.
To be honest,
I have also asked
another person for help.
If the three of us go,
I’m pretty confident that we will get there.
But don't worry Brother Ceng,
we will divide equally
the treasures we will find.
Take your time to consider my offer.
If you agree,
in one month,
use this jade to teleport to my fragment.
Brother Ceng,
I hope you will join me !
First of all, I need to recover.
I'd rather not take any risks
A few days later
Celestial spiritual energy
before the Soul Transformation breakthrough
cannot be used.
It's a poison if I try to absorb it before that point.
Fortunately, I gained a lot from this trip.
This is a naturally formed celestial jade.
The celestial spiritual energy inside it
is way stronger than the ones I condensed.
To cultivate after Soul Transformation,
this one is even more efficient.
But this thing doesn't look
like a defensive artifact.
What an ingenious technique !
It turns out this jade was carved by an ancient Celestial !
Tian Bao
Heavenly Treasure Celestial
I am Tian Bao, the Heavenly Treasure Celestial.
I have always dreamed of creating
the most powerful artifact in existence.
This dream of mine has ended
with the destruction of the Celestial Realm.
I have sealed my God Slaying Chariot in a cave.
If someone ever obtains this jade,
please retrieve it.
The God Slaying Chariot ?
This artifact
might still be in Tian Bao's cave !
A celestial artifact is incomparable
to artifacts of our world.
I must not miss
this opportunity.
10 days later
Stone Forest Fragment
Rain Celestial Realm
I have already searched all the fragments
of the Da Lou Sword Sect.
The Celestial Realm is vast,
if the cave isn't somewhere I can teleport to,
it will take me a long time to find.
Fellow cultivator,
save me !
Sima Yun
Shattered Silver Planet, Kui Shui Sect
Early stage Soul Formation
Fellow cultivator,
this has nothing to do with you.
Please leave.
He tried to steal my celestial jade.
If you help me to kill him,
we can split evenly !
Nonsense !
You're the one that stole from me.
We both come from planet Suzaku,
help me this once !
Scram !
Don't get me involved in this matter between you two.
Since you aren't willing to help,
then I might as well pass the buck.
I don't want
this celestial jade anymore !
Thank you.
I am Sima Yun from the Kui Shui Sect.
And fellow cultivator is ?
Ceng Niu.
Fellow cultivator Ceng,
I have been searching here for a few days,
there is no more celestial spiritual energy left.
Don't waste your time.
I don't know if you have any teleportation formations locations.
But if you do,
maybe we can exchange them.
He should also have a map of teleportation formations given by his sect.
What will you exchange with me ?
This person has 5 fragments
on the western side.
Fellow cultivator Ceng,
my map has 21 fragments
and 8 of them overlap with yours.
How about we trade
after you wipe off a few.
Fellow cultivator Ceng,
if you have the chance to come to my planet,
I’ll certainly welcome you.
Sure.
I shall take my leave.
Since that bastard tried to steal from me,
I will definitely not let him get away.
It seems that
the fragments of the Da Lou Sword Sect
were just the tip of the iceberg of the Celestial Realm.
Tiger Mountain Fragment
Rain Celestial Realm
I found it !
A tiger-shaped mountain ?
Such a place really exists ?
Celestial Tian Bao's cave
Tiger Mountain Fragment
Rain Celestial Realm
It seems that it has already been looted.
That's a shame, it was so hard to find this place.
The God Slaying Chariot
is sealed in the 10th room of the cave,
waiting for the one destined for it.
There are only 9 rooms in this cave.
Where is the 10th ?
The God Slaying Chariot is my life's work.
If it can be completed,
I...
won't have any regrets.
The cave is sinking.
Even if people found this cave, very few would be able
to find the room with the real treasure inside.
I don't know
what's in this room.
God Slaying Chariots
It looks like a celestial beast
that has come back to life.
This is
the God Slaying Chariot !
Fei
Soul of the God Slaying Chariot
What an overwhelming pressure !
The smallest of those beasts
is stronger than the 9-headed dragon in the Land of the Ancient God.
Although the jade didn't record the name of those beasts,
it did mention that
each chariot has chains to bind them.
So they can't move more than 9 meters away.
Using the God Slaying Chariot
with my Soul Formation cultivation
is impossible.
I can only seal these beasts for now.
Celestial Tian Bao wouldn't have thought that
his inestimable celestial artifacts would end up
in the hands of an Early stage Soul Formation.
Seal !
This God Slaying Chariot is so ingenious,
it's being powered by the beast soul inside.
I'm sure that
its power won't disappoint me.
This is the smallest of the 3 beasts
so maybe I can use the Beast Trap on it.
But even if the Beast Trap works,
will I be able to withstand
the absorption of spiritual energy ?
The harvest on this trip
has been very good.
But it also was dangerous.
If anything had gone wrong during that fragment collapse,
I would be dead by now.
Therefore,
I have to carefully consider
Chi Hu's invitation.
Not to mention the 3 celestial swords,
the celestial jade coffin
will be crucial for my future Soul Transformation.
As long as my cultivation reaches Soul Transformation,
I will be able to wake up Senior Situ.
I can also bring some
celestial herbs back to Wan'er.
Central Cold Fragment Entrance
Rain Celestial Realm
They're here.
I just don't know
which one it is.
Fellow cultivator Red Butterfly,
I've been waiting for you.
If what you said is false,
I won’t let this end so easily !
Fellow cultivator Red Butterfly can relax.
This jade was made
by my Giant Demon Clan’s Ancestor, Xi Zu.
He should have no reason to lie.
Xi Zu ?
On planet Suzaku,
my Giant Demon Clan and your country of Xue Yue
are the only non natives to the planet.
Xi Zu and your master were friends.
How could I lie to you ?
Since it was recorded by Xi Zu himself,
then I'll believe you and go on this trip.
The only treasure I want
is that jade coffin.
It must be mine !
She really is too overbearing.
Fellow cultivator Red Butterfly,
this matter is not so easily decided.
After all, besides the two of us,
one more person
should also join us on this trip.
I've promised him that
if the three of us work together,
we would split
all the treasures we find
evenly among us.
Since I'm the young master of the Giant Demon Clan,
I must keep my word.
Oh ?
And who is it ?
Ceng Niu.
Just like you and me,
he comes from planet Suzaku.
From planet Suzaku ?
Brother Ceng !
So you did come afterall.
It's you !
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust
like water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,
the truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death
are like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,
to cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled
because half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate
to ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage
to pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand
the hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers
while prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,
the law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.
Reincarnation is not to be feared.